[{"answer": "Thanks for coming over, Annie.  I really appreciate it", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 14, "question": "", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Its no problem", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 15, "question": "Thanks for coming over, Annie.  I really appreciate it", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Would you like a cup of coffee and a piece of cake", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Its no problem", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Sure.  That sounds nice", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Would you like a cup of coffee and a piece of cake", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Cream and sugar", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Sure.  That sounds nice", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": "No thanks.  I take my coffee black", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Cream and sugar", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " OK.  Here you go", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 20, "question": "No thanks.  I take my coffee black", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Wow!  That cake looks delicious!  Is it homemade", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 21, "question": " OK.  Here you go", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Yep.  I baked it myself this morning", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Wow!  That cake looks delicious!  Is it homemade", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Well, thanks.  I havent had homemade cake in a long time", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Yep.  I baked it myself this morning", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Youre welcome.  So, I told you that I was thinking of applying to your office", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Well, thanks.  I havent had homemade cake in a long time", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " UmmHmm", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Youre welcome.  So, I told you that I was thinking of applying to your office", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " Do you mind if I ask you a couple of questions about the office", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 32, "question": " UmmHmm", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " No, not at all.  Go ahead", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 33, "question": " Do you mind if I ask you a couple of questions about the office", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " I just have a few questions about their policies.  Like, How long do you get for ", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 34, "question": " No, not at all.  Go ahead", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Everyone gets an hour for lunch", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 38, "question": " I just have a few questions about their policies.  Like, How long do you get for ", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Are they strict", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Everyone gets an hour for lunch", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " What do you mean", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 40, "question": " Are they strict", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Like if you took an hour and fifteen minutes for lunch.  Would you get in ho", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 41, "question": " What do you mean", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": "Oh, no.  Theyre pretty relaxed there.  No one really cares how long you take fo", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Like if you took an hour and fifteen minutes for lunch.  Would you get in ho", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " That sounds good.  What about working hours?  Do you have to get there at ", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 49, "question": "Oh, no.  Theyre pretty relaxed there.  No one really cares how long you take fo", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": "Well, official work hours are from 8-5.  But, if youre a little late or leave a littl", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 53, "question": " That sounds good.  What about working hours?  Do you have to get there at ", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " That sounds so nice.  At my last job if we left even two minutes early, our bos", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 58, "question": "Well, official work hours are from 8-5.  But, if youre a little late or leave a littl", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " I dont think thats ever happened at my office", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 62, "question": " That sounds so nice.  At my last job if we left even two minutes early, our bos", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " OK.  Lets see What else did I want to ask you.?  Oh, yeah.  Dress code", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 63, "question": " I dont think thats ever happened at my office", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Its pretty much business casual there.  You wouldnt have to wear a suit and tie", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 67, "question": " OK.  Lets see What else did I want to ask you.?  Oh, yeah.  Dress code", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " Thats good too.  I hate wearing a tie!  Theyre so uncomfortable", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Its pretty much business casual there.  You wouldnt have to wear a suit and tie", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Yeah.  Its nice to be able to dress a little more relaxed at the office.  It doe", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 76, "question": " Thats good too.  I hate wearing a tie!  Theyre so uncomfortable", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " OK.  One last question and then Im done grilling you.  How many vacation day", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 80, "question": " Yeah.  Its nice to be able to dress a little more relaxed at the office.  It doe", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " The vacation policy is good at the office too.  You get 8 hours of vacation eac", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 84, "question": " OK.  One last question and then Im done grilling you.  How many vacation day", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " It sounds like the company has some really good policies", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 89, "question": " The vacation policy is good at the office too.  You get 8 hours of vacation eac", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " They do.  They treat their employees very well.  Id definitely recommend you t", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 90, "question": " It sounds like the company has some really good policies", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " I think I probably will.  You want more coffee", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 94, "question": " They do.  They treat their employees very well.  Id definitely recommend you t", "qSentId": 93},{"answer": " Sure.  Ill have one more cup", "docId": "03-02", "aSentId": 95, "question": " I think I probably will.  You want more coffee", "qSentId": 94}]
